{
    "subject": "Akhenaten",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Nefertiti",
    "human_readable": "Akhenaten is married to Nefertiti.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9151514768600464,
            "question": "To whom was Akhenaten married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9041568636894226,
            "question": "What relationship exists between Akhenaten and Nefertiti?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8862252235412598,
            "question": "Who is married to Nefertiti?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8840414881706238,
            "question": "Is Nefertiti married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8606698513031006,
            "question": "Name the wife of Akhenaten."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8124661445617676,
            "question": "Who was Akhenaten's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7243357300758362,
            "question": "Can you tell me the name of Akhenaten's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6690730452537537,
            "question": "Who is Akhenaten?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6389294266700745,
            "question": "What is the name of Nefertiti's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45431241393089294,
            "question": "Who is Akhenaten's consort?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Akhenaten is married to Nefertiti.",
            "html": "yago_21881_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Nefertiti's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_21881_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Akhenaten?",
            "html": "yago_21881_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me the name of Akhenaten's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_21881_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21881_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21881_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21881_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21881_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21881_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21881_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21881_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21881_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21881_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21881_52.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide several instances where it is stated that Nefertiti was the wife of Pharaoh Akhenaten, making the triple correct."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide several references that support the statement that Akhenaten was married to Nefertiti. For example, multiple files mention their marital relationship, including details about Nefertiti being his Great Royal Wife and the fact that they had children together."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}